Okay we have our pasta boiling, we have our sauce, we just added the mushrooms too together.
And now we’re going to show you how we’re going to peel our beautiful shrimp.
Now these are called Gulf Pink Shrimp, so they come from the Gulf of Mexico.
I prefer these over the ones from Thailand, Tiger Shrimp, but that’s just my own taste, you can do it.
So what you want to do is you can see the shells on these are very, very light.
So go ahead and take that first part off and just pull them right out, just like that.
Sometimes, with these sizes of shrimp you won’t really find a mud vein too much in the, the back of them.
Don’t worry if you, if you get the bigger shrimp, sometimes they do.
All you need to do is just run the blade of the knife around the back, and just pull it right out and just rinse it and you’ll be fine.
But these are just perfect for this, so you just go ahead and grab it again, take that top part off and just pull it right out.
See the legs and all of that come out, don’t be squeamish about this, this is real easy and your reward is wonderful.
So, and again, we’ll want to rinse these once we’re done but see how this just pulls right out, just by grasping the tail, sort of like a handle.
So what we want to do is probably about five or six, of these per person, at about this size, this is probably about a, what they call a thirty-one to thirty-five count shrimp, which means there is thirty-one to thirty-five shrimp per pound.